So we are very fortunate to have another guest on the stage,
Ms. Lu Bikang, a guest from the Art Center of Guangdong.
She will share with you the content of the personal production process and the high-end body movement.
Let's welcome Ms. Lu Bikang.
Hello, everyone. I'm Lu Bikang, from the Art Center of Guangdong.
I'm also a supporter.
I've worked with Ms. Lu Bikang before.
Before we start, let's take a look at the content of my project.
Let's start with the big picture.
Okay, let's start with the big picture.
The content of this presentation is the process of my personal production.
And there are some...
Some people are working on the body movement.
For example, when they are working on the two sides,
it's like an insertion.
Or some...
What do you call this?
This is called a band.
It will be deformed.
It will be softened.
I can provide an idea here.
And then...
The next one is a few angles.
Let's take a look.
Actually, we...
The teacher has already talked a lot about it.
I don't have anything to say.
So let's take a look.
Actually, I'm an animation.
With animation,
I can show more...
First of all,
we use this...
We use this...
To make it...
We use this in dosing.
That way...
It's...
To controlled together...
To this...
It will have...
The...
For example, the table...
Will be nicely controlled...
It will be nicely controlled...
And installed.
At first,
It was very boring.
For this kind of thing, you can do whatever you want with ZP.
And then, it's the same, select the version.
After you open the UI, you can use the version for it.
And then, there's actually not much to do with this.
I think everyone should know this, so I'll just go ahead and do it.
This is not the main thing, it's not the main thing.
And then we'll import, if we import, we'll choose OPG.
And then we'll choose the one we just did.
Alright, change to the original one.
And then, we'll change to the version version.
And it'll come in.
It may look messy right now, but once you do the calculations, they'll show.
What we're going to do now is the edge selection.
So when it comes in, it won't be smooth.
We're going to make it a bit smoother.
And we can use this, use this red zone.
I'm sorry.
With this tool, we can use the backslide tool to make a line.
At this time, we will make it symmetrical.
There are a lot of goals, a lot of symmetry.
Then we will select it first.
Select this symmetry first.
After that, we will cut it open and crack it open.
After cracking it open, we will delete that thing.
We only need half of it.
Then we will do it in the same way.
When we do it in the same way, we will do it in the same way.
Because these points are one by one.
So it's not that perfect.
Use this method to make the curve smoother.
And it's easy to control.
If this backslide is to be controlled,
we can do it like this.
We can do it like this.
It's more convenient to do this adjustment.
If this one should actually be here.
There are two sections.
Then I will be lazy.
I didn't do it so carefully.
Sometimes it's more terrible when people get excited.
Then,
Yes, these places are a little bit like this.
In fact, it's not completely.
I can do it.
But I don't think it's a problem to sit down.
Then it's symmetrical.
Symmetry can be made.
Then quickly do all the places all at once.
Then the clothes are basically like this.
Then the specific method.
In fact, there were a lot of big and small ones before.
I won't talk about these things anymore.
Then this is to make the bag shape.
The bag in front of the chest.
When we started doing it,
we didn't let him do it so carefully.
Just do a rough guess.
Give the clothes to you first.
There is a kind of focus.
Then we use the freeze function more.
The freeze function is very useful.
Very useful.
How to say?
Just let other things do a calculation first.
It doesn't disperse.
Then it can reduce some calculation and some transformation.
The students who use it may know.
That is to say, a lot of cloth is glued together.
If you squeeze it, there is a possibility that there will be a collision.
Then it will explode.
This kind of situation is very.
It's easy to happen.
This is a tool that can insert some questions.
There will always be some trouble.
Then we just.
Simply this.
Put it on.
Then we just.
Make a half of this.
Adjust it.
When we do things.
Don't do it very carefully from the beginning.
That is to say, you can give yourself some space.
Give yourself a back.
Don't be so dead.
Be a person.
Just be happy.
Then.
Anyway, in this.
Start.
Old color B's favorite.
This bag skirt.
Then it's two pieces of fabric.
In fact, doing that.
Doing this.
The material is actually not so.
You just have to match this.
The shape.
At this time.
You can see the skirt inside.
The clothes inside.
He desperately wants to run out.
At this time.
We can increase it.
He has a lot of space.
Yes.
He jumped.
It doesn't matter.
There is one in the back.
Then go to change his layer.
His value is equivalent to a value.
The higher the result, the higher the value.
Then you can go.
To collect the back of your front.
No.
Inside and outside.
Wrong.
Then just turn around like this.
Turn around.
This.
Of course, it depends on the performance of your machine.
The performance of your machine.
And your.
The top.
This.
The bottom.
The top.
This.
The bottom.
Nice.
Now.
I'm going with the bottom.
Yes.
This.
Right.
Can you see this.
Next.
How do you look.
And then it's pretty much like this.
Coming here is the production of a body.
The body was not delivered just now.
Let's hurry up and don't do everything.
Then we will hurry up and do other things together.
At the same time, it's the same as drawing a sketch.
That is, you can't cut a point too much.
It's perfectly drawn and very delicate.
But your mouth and other organs are not drawn.
This is not good.
Then let's do the belt on the body.
Let's make the body of the model on it.
Let it have a low number.
Otherwise it will fall down.
Then this thing seems to be.
There is nothing to look at.
Someone asked me why I had to grab this thing.
I have to put it on for so long.
I forgot to cut it.
It seems to be comfortable.
I'm sorry.
Then we look at it.
Then there is also a piece at the back.
Sew it.
Stick it on.
Stick it.
Then find the right distance.
Then the other side is also sewed.
After sewing, we click on it.
Then it can be attached.
The other side can also be sewed.
This has been done to a stage.
The back is temporarily folded up.
There are other designs at the back.
Because of the rationality.
Let him say a little.
This is a more reasonable way.
It looks good and it is reasonable.
Mr. Huotang.
Then this place is.
This is the part of the steel.
That is, the part of the steel joint.
First of all, we should.
That is, we have to put this steel place.
That is to say, the surface of the surface.
Is to be divided out.
Then separate it one by one.
Separate.
Give it a very, very, very.
Very hard material.
Let it stand up.
Then look at my value.
Has been given a very high value.
Just make it harder.
Don't let it have too many wrinkles.
Then the color is also changed.
Changed to a golden yellow.
Make him feel.
Make you feel.
That is to say.
He is a.
Is a.
This.
Then.
Look at what you are doing now.
Give him a color.
In this.
Can actually change the color.
Let him do something like metal.
Now it's a thin.
Thin.
We can.
Let him open the double side.
Now I haven't opened it.
What are you doing now?
Yes.
Give him the width.
Now.
After the three pieces are made.
Yes, this side can.
This side can be changed.
This one is not good.
Then I changed it.
Three millimeters.
It's thicker than the other materials.
And it should be.
I think it's thick.
The material is even better.
It's not easy to get the fabric.
There is no need to make it.
It is not.
Then that shape.
That is to help him.
Still have to go with.
The shape you want.
I want to update it, because when the time comes, this piece of board can be passed through, and it will form a buckle.
It will form a patch mode, something like that.
Just to let it have a buckle.
Just to let it turn around and buckle.
Right now, the board outside is facing the opposite direction.
It's facing the opposite direction.
Because when it's facing the opposite direction, it doesn't show the correct direction.
So you have to be careful.
At this time, the structure is completed.
Let it be complete around this piece of paper.
This way, it will be more precise.
When the time comes, it will be more reasonable.
It will be more accurate.
It will have the feeling of a circle.
Then adjust it again.
It still needs to take a little bit of time.
Take a little bit of time to adjust it.
Then...
Other places are also done in the same way.
Then it depends on what your structure is like.
It depends on the specific question and specific update.
Other places are done the same way.
It's not moving.
It's stuck.
It moves.
The golden handle.
It can't be cut off.
It's a bit hasty to cut.
Then quickly make the connection structure of various places.
MD can also be done.
Then...
But don't do it too much.
There is a degree that you have to hold on to.
I don't want to do the same thing as before.
I want to take it out on its own.
I want to make the packaging on its own.
I don't want the clothes to be part of the calculation.
I will make the clothes into an OPG and make it into an avatar.
This will reduce the amount of calculation.
Remember to use one side when you make it.
If you use two sides, there will be this kind of pressure on the machine.
Because the other side will also be involved in the collision.
At this time, I will do the packaging.
There is an internal big package first.
I designed an internal big package.
There are two small packages outside.
In this way, the space will be bigger.
I will use a very simple face.
This is good.
In fact, the method is the same.
There are several faces.
Then make the material a little harder.
Don't have so much focus.
If you are accurate, you can go to the later stage.
Or give it a calculation.
In the early stage, when you make the shape.
Don't think too much.
This is also a steel structure.
Then we can make it.
Make it in this way.
In fact, if you think this method is more troublesome.
In fact, you can also use the external modeling method.
Make it well and then pour it in.
Then tie the wire.
Let it be fixed.
In fact, it can also be done.
The method is the same as today.
The main thing is the four of us.
Then it's basically done here.
Take a look again.
See if there are any problems that can be solved.
It should be like this.
Do more observation.
Do more things.
It doesn't have to be.
This is also a thing.
Observe more.
Back and forth.
Then.
It doesn't have to be so long.
Then I look at the camera.
Look at the camera.
Look at your own things.
Then we can get back.
Before we get back.
We take off the clothes first.
Comfort.
Then.
All the bags.
Just now we took all the bags.
We put them together.
After we put them together.
All is rebuilt.
Yes.
It doesn't shake.
Then we worthy.
There clothes.
Yes.
If there is before.
It's wrong.
OK.
All.
Yes.
Minus.
It responsibility.
Lucky some.
This should be some basic design.
I don't think everyone here has a problem with it.
And then I'll let him sort it out a little bit.
Every time he goes to redo it, there will be a progress bar.
When I was a machine, I was a machine seven or seven and a half years ago.
Maybe everyone here now is 309.
I don't care about the details anymore.
Anyway, the machine is also a part of the hardware.
And now I'm going to open this package.
After opening the package, the two of us will make an interaction.
And at this time, its point is that its distribution is relatively high.
So we need more time.
Let him go.
It's a stable state of interaction.
And then this side should take the skirt.
I didn't go to the skirt.
Because it's actually more important.
Just break the shape of it.
In fact, this is also a reference.
I don't have too many settings.
And then.
All the so-called frozen places.
All of them.
All of them are frozen.
After freezing, you can.
You can do the calculation again.
Let them have a good one as a whole.
It's a nice one.
So it's a cross.
And then maybe it'll take a little bit of time at this time.
It takes a little bit of time.
Half an hour.
Then you can go out.
You can eat fish.
You can go out and drink coffee.
At this time, it depends on your personal hobbies.
Then the hobby of raising fish will be different.
Then at this time, you can wait for a while.
And then his.
The calculation is more intensive.
At this time, we came to the calculation of this UB.
UB is.
You can directly put his UB in the routine.
So we.
The movement of my steel body.
In fact, with this UB.
There is a very, very big relationship.
That is.
That is, you must make this UB full in the early stage.
Basically, in the later stage.
That is.
That is, this clothes has done almost.
There is already a 70% or 80% of this.
The effect.
Then your UB can be confirmed.
Unless.
Unless you are doing a project.
Suddenly said that this design needs to be changed.
Then there is no way.
If it is a small design.
Then there is no problem.
But if the whole shape is changed.
Then certainly.
But in the work.
There must be another time calculation.
That is to say.
Not to say that it is.
Another thing.
That is.
In our department.
Maybe in some other departments.
Their time calculation.
It's more personal.
We are some support departments.
That is.
There may not be so much hurry.
Do some beautiful things.
Maybe it will take a little longer.
Then.
That is.
We put this.
This.
Each version.
Wait.
Wait for this.
Stand.
Stand the biggest.
At that time.
We draw the map.
It's easy to draw.
That is.
There are more pixels.
To call it.
This.
Then we can.
Yes.
We have to go to this version.
All three.
Absolutely.
Can't waste.
to transfer it to the clothes in a UV way.
Some people said that you can directly press D to make it flat.
I prefer to make it look like a UV.
It's easier to find.
It's up to you.
This is a work.
It's a must-have for a steel work.
Because the steel work is very complicated now.
It may cause some deformation.
I will make it into a black-and-white model.
There is a pattern.
And then...
To put it simply,
put its shape...
Put its shape...
Don't make it too much.
There is only one...
You may think that there is only one triangle.
The triangle will not have three points.
If it's a square,
there may be two more points.
There may be...
There may be a problem.
If you look at it in principle,
You can use 3D, but I don't have a special machine here.
I just use this.
4D.
But the problem is not that big.
Maybe when you encounter a problem, you can try again.
Sometimes you do things while doing experiments.
It doesn't matter in some places.
Just let it protect you.
Sometimes it doesn't work.
You have to stick to your dreams.
Then you have to do it.
It's done.
When it's done,
we can freeze it like this.
Now it's time to pass the UB.
We use the attribute transfer method.
The attribute transfer is a big function that surrounds this.
This is a basic function.
Then we do a lot of things through it.
Now we pass the UB information through it.
Through this,
we pass the material.
We pass the material through it.
It just went up.
Now,
we still use the attribute transfer method.
We pass the top-end information
to this
T-Pose.
In this way,
the
attribute sheet
becomes a very clean image.
Then we use this
band shape.
This is a
switch.
This is a horizontal and a final
space position switch.
In this way,
we can do a
modeling when it's horizontal.
For example,
this is a model that I used before.
I made one
and used it.
In theory, it should be a simple one first
and then see what happens.
But in order to save time,
I will use it directly.
Let's start over.
I missed one.
This is to make a package.
Let's go to this.
You can see that there is a package on this side.
The package is equivalent to
the version
to wrap this model.
Then it can be linked.
It slides over.
You can see that it is already in a correct position.
Then we put the other unnecessary information.
Let's take a look at this.
This is a plug-in.
There is no problem with this plug-in.
Then its head
seems to be a problem.
It is not plugged in.
Then we just
in this
in this actual picture,
it is recommended not to use the dot face to edit.
Because it is very likely to cause some problems.
So we use
the most common
coordinate change to
make its position the best.
Then if you have some points,
you can go back to
the flat model
to edit.
This is a point to pay attention to.
Because I have tried it before.
So I want to
give you a proper review.
At this point,
we have completed
all the solid points.
That is, we have put it on.
Then it starts to be UV.
Then these little things start to be UV.
Then these materials can be
Then we can start to put this
material on.
I
may
make it 50%
or
I will
make some color additions
or some color adjustments.
Try to make it have a color distinction.
Just roughly.
Don't be too careful.
It is equivalent to
the vitality of your own.
Don't let yourself
make mistakes.
Then this one.
This one is reasonable.
Just make its
panel.
Make it a
quadrilateral.
One is a good sculpture.
The second is a good decoration.
Look at this quadrilateral.
This quadrilateral is so beautiful.
This is an advantage.
It is also an advantage.
Then we will
make it by hand.
You can make it by hand.
Then this one.
At that time, I didn't make
a lot of details.
At this time, you can use
the way I did
to make a detail add-on.
In MP1, I made some
edges, or some
very small structures.
Or a very deep edge.
It is more...
How can I say?
I can't say it is more...
In this case,
I can't say it is more suitable.
It is not very convenient.
Maybe G3 or other ways.
We can use the model
to make it
with details.
After we finish the details,
we can use the way I did.
It is the same as the steel.
But the bottom of
the drive
is a...
How can I say?
Yes, it is done.
Some details have been
put away.
This is the fabric.
The fabric will be cleaner.
There will be some details in these places.
Like this one.
I didn't look at it.
Some steel is
made by hand.
Then we
go back to the screen again.
All these small structures
are done.
After they are done,
we can let them
match each other
with the corresponding
red panel.
The red panel can be
called
a small group.
It will lead these
rendering models.
The rendering model is a dark green
rendering model.
It is only used for rendering.
The dark green
rendering model.
To make it look like itself.
Then we use
the package to wrap it up.
It is like a red
model with
a high heat.
Then
this step is
because the current
model is scattered.
It is inconvenient for us to transmit.
So we use the overall model
to give
a separate
to make a
The speed of reading may be high, I didn't do a lot of practice, I did a lot of online classes
Anyway, both are good, A, B, C are more convenient
Then we can't get into this, after we can't get into it
Then there will be an animation
I just made an animation, then we choose the resolution, choose this, click on this record
It's actually an animation module, and many people should have used it
Then start the calculation, of course, this calculation is not that smooth, I just added 100 times
Then this came to this, put this thing in
This is the state of the pose just now
Then we go to do a property transfer
In fact, this property transfer also includes this soul
Then we pass it to this UU teacher
I didn't turn on the resolution just now
Then pass it
This thank you very much, I may have cut this out
This order has come
He just showed me
And then I have actually missed a little bit in the middle
It's the latter, in fact, the middle
I did some of the material
But I don't think it's quite enough, so the material is not particularly clear
Sometimes if you want to see more details, you can go to my website
When you arrive in my small town, you can make an advertisement for yourself.
This is the lighting environment setting.
This is the main light, this is the secondary light, and this is the back light.
And then there is the environment light.
The environment light is used to detect the wind from the metal.
And then there is the top light, the sky light.
The sky light will send a light blue color from the top to the bottom of the sky.
But when it comes to lighting, I usually use a single light to check the lighting effect.
Because we don't use this as a focus right now.
So we use V-Ray to do it.
V-Ray has a lot of knowledge about GPUs.
So I recommend everyone to consider GPUs more if you want to play.
Because CPUs need to be updated.
If you want to update a CPU, you need to update the corresponding components.
For example, you need to update the components in the store.
But if you only want to use CPUs, you only need to update the graphics card.
Although the graphics card is expensive, its cost is relatively small.
And it's more convenient.
Now...
Just plug in the PCIe card.
And then we'll click on Show.
And then let it run.
The data here seems to be in the graphics card.
And then...
It's a little hard.
I've already checked it.
If it's the last one, I'll check it.
Now we see that...
1.X1080-7i.
This is because it's a little slow.
Now the human race is 301, 307, and 309.
And then we...
If we plug it in, it can show up in the graphics card.
And then we basically...
And then you can change the pose.
Of course, you can go to the back, go to PS, go to AE, or...
If you have animation, you can go to...
For example, if you have a tent table, you can have a special animation.
You can go to...
Do a post-processing.
Adjust the color.
And then pull the contrast.
And then put his...
Because I think...
Oh, it's already started.
No, it's over anyway.
And then the post-processing is also...
I think it's more important.
If it's just a single rendering.
For example, if you want to add...
Just want to add some exposure.
I think the post-processing is better.
Just...
Sometimes when I work, I have some friends who like to bother me.
A very simple post-processing.
He doesn't want to ask 3D to play a...
Turn on the lights.
Then it's very smooth.
So I think...
Ghost.
There is no post-processing.
Try to use post-processing.
Then I'll...
I can...
Thank you.
Do you have any questions at all?
Questions.
OK.
Hello.
I'd like to ask you about the operation
of the property transfer.
When did you...
The position?
Yeah, the position.
It doesn't have to be for the property transfer.
Wait.
Let me turn it to that.
To the interface.
This one.
This interface.
It's actually...
It has 2 models.
One is the content you need to transmit.
On top is the vertex composition.
It is the pointer to transmit.
And this is the vertex normal.
It can also transmit the image of the vertex.
And UV.
Two of the same thing.
You can also transmit its UV.
There are different UVs in the same model.
But you have to put all of its UVs together.
You have to have the same UV.
You can use this function.
This is the content you need to transmit.
What do you want to transmit?
Is it the point or the vertex?
Next is the sample.
Now I am using the same UV.
You can see in this box.
The first box is in the first line.
The first line corresponding to the outfit.
You can think of it as point-to-point correspondence.
It is not point-to-point correspondence.
It is in the space.
Any pixel point.
It is not so clear.
Maybe I am talking too much.
It is equivalent to.
You cut the square into 10,000 points.
There are 10,000 points in 10,000 points.
Cut into 1,000 points.
There are 1,000 points.
It can match the point to the model.
The UV is locked on this model.
Then you can transmit it.
You can go back and try it.
You can use UV.
You can also use the world's coordinates.
The world's coordinates.
Just stick the two models very close together.
Stick it very close together.
Then there is this function.
Then you can also use this top-down.
The top-down is the top of the two models.
And the way of the top is the same.
Then you can do something like this.
Or there are a lot of things.
For example, after your ground model is made.
What's your name?
Play side.
If the ground model is done.
But you fall out.
Or it falls out from another ground.
And it's broken again.
You can take a good one.
Is this a good one?
A model of a plane of ground.
Through UV or through the holder.
Or go through this material.
Go back.
Fall back.
You should understand this.
OK.
I will try it.
We need to take a look.
Relative tutorial.
You can.
Or I speak better.
I don't know.
I don't want to wake him up.
He is still sleeping.
He is too sleepy.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
I just want to ask,
when you were giving a message to yourself,
was it a B站 account or something?
Yes, it was a B Stand account.
It was Nubing.
Nubing.
Yes, yes, yes.
I usually do some sharing,
so I wanted to take a look at it.
Are there any other questions?
When you watch the live broadcast online,
please pay attention to
Mr. Nubing's B Stand account.
Remember to click the three dots.
Okay.
If there are no more questions,
we will leave now.
Thank you for your time.